(Leonard:)I checked the
App Store.
(Leonard:)No one is doing
(Leonard:)handwriting-recognition
differential equation solving.
(Sheldon:)Oh, dear Lord, shush.
(Raj(pressing button on camera phone. Camera makes a fart noise):)What?
(Sheldon:)You have so few good ideas,
Leonard.
(Sheldon:)And you're just going
to spill the beans
(Sheldon:)in front of an outsider?
(Penny:)Who, me?
(Howard:)Sheldon, I don't think
Penny cares
(Howard:)about handwriting-recognition
based differential...
♪ The stars at night
are big and bright ♪
♪ Deep in the heart
of Texas... ♪
(Leonard:)She's not going
to steal our idea.
(Penny:)What idea?
We're gonna write an application...
♪ The prairie sky
is wide and high ♪
♪ Deep in the heart... ♪
(Penny:)Okay, stop, stop!
♪ Of Texas. ♪
(Penny:)Whatever your secret is,
(Penny:)I'm sure it's boring,
so I'm not interested.
(Leonard:)It's not boring at all.
(Leonard:)You see,
in higher order mathematics,
(Leonard:)there are certain sets
(Leonard:)of equations that...
Bored.
(Leonard:)Satisfied?